



Luiz Miguel Silva Lima

Date of birth: 03/01/2000 | **Phone number:** (+351) 925002615 (Mobile) |

Email address: miguelsl2000@gmail.com | Website: www.silvalima.dev |

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/miguelsilvalima/ | **GitHub:**

https://github.com/Aeziren

Address: 2490-126, Ourém (Willing to Relocate), Portugal (Home)

ABOUT ME

I am a Freelancer Software Developer with a strong foundation in Python and experience in back end tools such as Django, Flask and SQL. Also, I am well-versed in software engineering tools and methodologies such as Docker, Git, CI/CD, Agile and RESTful APIs. Additionally, I have solid knowledge in Cybersecurity and practical experience with the deployment and management of applications in cloud environments.

Due to my long-standing passion for the technology field and my professional background, I am confident in my ability to quickly adapt to any work environment and acquire the necessary skills to meet the specific demands of a project.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - CURRENT Remote

BACKEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER SELF-EMPLOYED

Currently working as a freelance software developer, using my skills in programming and databases to maintain and improve the backend of a wide array of applications.

Tech Stack: Python, Django, Javascript, RESTful API, SQL, Google Cloud Platform, Git, CI/CD

01/2022 - 12/2022 Batalha, Portugal

FACTORY OPERATOR MATCERÂMICA

Collaborated with a diverse team to ensure efficient production processes, where, strong teamwork and communication skills is needed in order to coordinate tasks with colleagues. Also, I played a vital role in quality assurance by conducting inspections and identifying defects in tableware products.

Skills: Time Management, Teamwork, Coordination, Effective Communication, Practical Thinking, Quality Assurance

2016 - 2021 Rio das Ostras, Brazil

COMPUTER MAINTENANCE SELF-EMPLOYED

Assembled computers with customized configurations based on client needs and instructions, always focusing quality. Also, resolved issues and performed routine maintenance.

Skills: Problem Solving, Analytical Skills, Hardware Knowledge, Verbal Skills, Continuous Learning, Responsibility, Self-Taught, Logical Thinking

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2022 - CURRENT Remote, Brazil

BACHELOR'S DEGREE, SOFTWARE ENGINEERING UNOPAR University

ASSOCIATE'S DEGREE, SYSTEM ANALYSIS AND DEVELOPMENT UNOPAR University

2016 - 2017 Rio das Ostras, Brazil

ASSEMBLY AND MAINTENANCE OF COMPUTERS AND CELLPHONES Prepara Cursos

2023 Remote

JUNIOR CYBERSECURITY ANALIST Cisco

DIGITAL SKILLS

Python | Django | JavaScript | C | Unit Testing | Flask | RESTful api | SQL | Linux | CSS | HTML | CI/CD | Docker | Agile | Git | Bootstrap | Databases | Cybersecurity | Object-Oriented Programming | Cloud Computing (GCP) | RegEx

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **PORTUGUESE**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C2	C2	C1	C1	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

PROJECTS

Social Network Website This site implement a RESTful API built using Django and use AJAX to interact with it. In this site you can register, modify your profile, create posts, follow other users and like their posts!

Links https://youtu.be/SnUs505cdOQ | https://github.com/Aeziren/social-network

E-commerce Website Marketplace website made using Django. Users can register, create their listings, and place bids and comments on other users listings.

Links https://github.com/Aeziren/e-commerce

Backup App Assign any folder in your system and this application will keep track of all changes on it and made a backup copy in a directory of your choice. All changes made will get logged in .txt file and in the console.

Links https://youtu.be/769DdzG_GBw | https://github.com/Aeziren/folder-mirror

Email Website A single page application where everything happens without the need to reload the page. Users can register, log in, navigate through their emails and send emails to other users.

Links https://github.com/Aeziren/email

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: A **Driving Licence:** B